Beyond the veil of night, on the other side
To those of you ten thousand miles away
Have you been well ?　As usual ?
A light flashes on old photographs
The scent of the city, the smile on your face
The early days are still vivid
Please remember
You and I, we've been running together
Watch over me
I'll sing here
for this Decade to come
As long as your voice reaches me
I'll be singing in my corner of this planet
for this Decade to come
It may be trivial　and only for yourself
But this is your one and only love song
for this Decade to come
Long before dots connected together
When you were still nobody
Fighting alone in painful times
You held up the lamp through the dark night roads
Your feelings, your melody
I won't forget, not matter how long it's been
Please remember
You and I, we've been running together
Watch over me
I'll sing here
for this Decade to come
We don't know when to give up
We'll be singing in our corner of this planet
for this Decade to come
Appearing and disappearing, floating in ordinary days
In this moment it shines bright, your one and only love song
for this Decade to come